<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SPJ</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="spj">SPJ</string>
    <string name="sport_professional">Sport Professional</string>
    <string name="football">Football</string>
    <string name="tennis">Tennis</string>
    <string name="basketball">Basketball</string>
    <string name="baseball">Baseball</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="_basketball">-Basketball</string>
    <string name="_football">-Football</string>
    <string name="_tennis">-Tennis</string>
    <string name="_baseball">-Baseball</string>
    <string name="go_to_the_sections_of_interest_and_follow_the_sports_news_in_real_time">Go to the sections of interest and follow the sports news in real time</string>
    <string name="you_can_also_see_the_top_best_players_of_2023_tennis_basketball_baseball_and_football">You can also see the top best players of 2023: tennis, basketball, baseball and football</string>
    <string name="if_you_want_to_read_all_the_sports_news_of_the_week_then_click_on_the_rectangle_in_the_navigation_bar">If you want to read all the sports news of the week, then click on the rectangle in the navigation bar</string>
    <string name="also_to_make_it_convenient_for_you_to_read_the_news_at_any_time_of_the_day_we_have_made_a_theme_change_function">Also, to make it convenient for you to read the news at any time of the day, we have made a theme change function</string>
    <string name="title_news1_basketball">RUZHENTSEV CAUSED PRIDE WITH HIS PLAYOFF PERFORMANCE. I WOULD LIKE OTHER RUSSIANS TO FOLLOW HIS PATH AS WELL</string>
    <string name="title_new2_basketball">Supernovae or Outgoing Ones. 10 main stars of the basketball World Cup-2023</string>
    <string name="title_new3_basketball">Will the USA regain its former greatness? Will Spain defend the title? What you need to know about the 2023 World Cup</string>
    <string name="title_new1_football">Will Dynamo sell another leader to Europe? Have you already found someone to replace Fomin with</string>
    <string name="title_new2_football">Spartak beat Dynamo in the Russian Cup. Abascal\'s experiments finally worked!</string>
    <string name="title_new3_football">Nigmatullin believes that Khudyakov should think about renting to another club</string>
    <string name="title_new1_tennis">Minus Khachanov and Potapov. Which of the Russians did not live up to expectations at the start of the US Open</string>
    <string name="title_new2_tennis">Medvedev\'s record start. The Russian won the first match at the US Open in accelerated mode</string>
    <string name="title_new3_tennis">Comfortable in the shadow of Djokovic and Alcatraz</string>
    <string name="title_new1_baseball">The World Baseball Confederation does not plan to allow Russians to enter the international arena yet</string>
    <string name="title_new2_baseball">"The smart Americans turned it into baseball." Why will Russian schoolchildren be taught lapta?</string>
    <string name="title_new3_baseball">Brailey St. Clair - a reason to love softball</string>
    <string name="desc_new1_basketball">Carsen Edwards becomes the newest addition to new Pablo Laso\'s project at FC Bayern Munich with a one-year deal and completes the team\'s guard rotation, according to the official information.</string>
    <string name="desc_new2_basketball">Carsen Edwards becomes the newest addition to new Pablo Laso\'s project at FC Bayern Munich with a one-year deal and completes the team\'s guard rotation, according to the official information.</string>
    <string name="desc_new3_basketball">Carsen Edwards becomes the newest addition to new Pablo Laso\'s project at FC Bayern Munich with a one-year deal and completes the team\'s guard rotation, according to the official information.</string>
    <string name="desc_new1_football">In previous years, Dynamo gained a reputation as a club that does not skimp on buying players and generous contracts. It turned out to be much worse to sell their players profitably. A flashy example is the case of Maximilian Philip, bought for 20 million and sold three times cheaper.</string>
    <string name="desc_new2_football">Former Lokomotiv goalkeeper Ruslan Nigmatullin expressed the opinion that Daniil Khudyakov, the goalkeeper of the railwaymen, should think about renting to get permanent playing practice.\n"
                    "In total, 19‑year-old Khudyakov has 34 matches for Lokomotiv, in which he conceded 61 goals.</string>
    <string name="desc_new3_football">Carsen Edwards becomes the newest addition to new Pablo Laso\'s project at FC Bayern Munich with a one-year deal and completes the team\'s guard rotation, according to the official information.</string>
    <string name="desc_new1_tennis">Carsen Edwards becomes the newest addition to new Pablo Las\'s project at FC Bayern Munich with a one-year deal and completes the team\'s guard rotation, according to the official information.</string>
    <string name="desc_new2_baseball">The latest recommendations of the International Olympic Committee (IOC) do not give the World Baseball and Softball Confederation (WBSC) grounds to return Russians and Belarusians to international competitions.\n"
                    "\"The latest recommendations of the IOC executive committee of March 28, 2023 do not apply to baseball and softball, as they provide that teams of athletes with Russian or Belarusian passports cannot be considered for participation in international sports competitions,\" the WBSC press service quoted TASS as saying.\n
                    On March 28, 2023, the IOC recommended that international sports federations allow Russian athletes who do not support their sports in a neutral status to start. At the same time, Russian and Belarusian athletes should not be represented in team sports.</string>
    <string name="desc_new3_baseball">The All-Russian Forum of school sports clubs held in Kazan on Thursday presented an unusual information guide. If your child or you are studying at school, then soon you will probably have to get acquainted with the game of bast shoes in physical education. It is not clear yet whether it will be in a mandatory format or whether it will be possible to choose it among other sports. Russian Russian bast shoes, we decided to find out from the president of the Russian Bast Shoes Federation of Russia and coach Sergey Fokin why the officials remembered Russian fun and what condition the Russian bast shoes are in now.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new1_basketball">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\n"
                    "He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new2_basketball">On Friday, August 25, the Basketball World Cup started in three countries — Japan, Indonesia and the Philippines, which will last until September 10. In this material, "SE" gathered the main stars of the tournament. With an important clarification: the list should not contain more than one representative from each national team.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new3_basketball">The 2023 World Cup will be the second of three in a row scheduled to be held in Asia,
                    between the 2019 tournament held in China and the upcoming 2027 World Cup in Qatar. It will also be the second
                    in history with the participation of 32 teams and the first to be held by more than one country. The championship
                    will have three hosts at once — the Philippines, Japan and Indonesia will host the preliminary stages, and the main matches will be held in the Philippines.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new1_football">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists,
                    and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\n
                    He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new2_football">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over
                    14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\n
                    He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new3_football">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\nHe helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new1_tennis">It is noteworthy that just a year ago at the US Open, a white streak in Khachanov\'s tennis career began. Karen finally managed to break through to the semifinals of the Grand Slam tournament, beating, in particular, Australian Nick Kyrgios — the offender Daniil Medvedev. And in the match for reaching the final, he gave a fight to Norwegian Kasper Ruud. As the Russian himself told, after that tournament he believed that he was able to achieve success at big tournaments. Thanks to this, he made a qualitative leap in results — he reached the semifinals at the Australian Open and the Indian Wells Masters and the quarterfinals of Roland Garros, returned to the top 10 of the ATP rankings after a long break.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new2_tennis">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists,
                    and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\n
                    He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new3_tennis">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists,
                    and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from RANDOM NEWS DELETE ME beyond the arc.\nHe helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new1_baseball">The number of subscribers in social networks of the native of Alabama is growing every day. The blue-eyed beauty, who now plays for the
                    Mississippi State College softball team, is a success with fans. And this is not surprising.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new2_baseball">\"The Russian national baseball team is going to Cuba in April for match meetings with the national and youth teams of this country, the tour will take place from April 3 to 17. It is planned to hold seven games, the exact days and times of meetings are being worked out together with the Cuban side. On Tuesday, the composition of the Russian national team will be approved, now the final preparations for the flight to Cuba are underway. During the visit to Cuba, it is planned to sign a cooperation agreement between the baseball federations of Russia and Cuba,\" TASS quoted Kisilev as saying.\n At the end of November, the European Executive Committee of the World Baseball and Softball Confederation suspended Russia from European competitions in the 2023 season. The decision concerns Russian athletes, coaches, specialists and officials of all levels and age groups. The ban on holding European and international baseball tournaments in the country was also extended.</string>
    <string name="paragraph1_new3_baseball">And suddenly we got a very emotional reaction to the news, not at all positive. We publish the cry of the soul of a person, which representatives
                    "of other federations of rare sports can surely join.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new1_basketball">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\n
                "The Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new2_basketball">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\nThe Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new3_basketball">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\nThe Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new1_football">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\nThe Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new2_football">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\nThe Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new3_football">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach €1.8 million in net.\nThe Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new1_tennis">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\n The Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new2_tennis">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\n The Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new3_tennis">According to Konstantinos Melayess from Gazzetta.gr, his total earnings will reach 1.8 million in net.\n The Greek sharpshooter previously had one year left on his deal.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new1_baseball" formatted="false">St. Clair quickly gained a huge number of subscribers: more than 230,000 on social networks.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new2_baseball">Dmitry Kiselyov, President of the Russian Baseball Federation, announced that the national team will travel to Cuba on April 3, where it will hold several matches with the national and youth teams of this country.</string>
    <string name="paragraph2_new3_baseball">Where have you been before? Come to your senses when they tear off the head of everything Russian?\n — I don\'t quite understand — where is the wave about this lapta module coming from?</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new1_basketball" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\nHe helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new2_basketball" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\nHe helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new3_basketball" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new1_football" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new2_football" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new3_football" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new1_tennis" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new2_tennis" formatted="false">Larentzakis, 29, appeared in 41 EuroLeague games last season and averaged 6.4 points, 1.8 rebounds, 1.0 assists, and 4.8 PIR over 14 minutes per contest while shooting 49.2% from mid-range and 37.2% from beyond the arc.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new3_tennis" formatted="false">Admittedly, the opponent in the first round Medvedev got, perhaps, the simplest of all possible. Hungarian Attila Balazs ended his career in 2014, but a couple of years later decided to resume performances. And for good reason — he made a breakthrough in the top 100 at the age of 30 years. In 2019, he sensationally reached the final of the ATP tournament in Umag, Croatia. In addition, he showed himself well at the \"challengers\", in particular, at the beginning of 2020, he beat Russian Aslan Karatsev in the final in Bangkok. Slowly, he reached the 76th position in the ranking, but then missed 14 months due to injury. \n After that, in 2022, he played in three \"challengers\", at Roland Garros and Wimbledon, but without success. Then I tried to come back last spring, but in Monte Carlo, Barcelona and Madrid I didn\'t take a single set in the qualifiers. Thus, he had no usual rating by August 2023. But according to the protected rating, the 34-year—old Balazh had the opportunityto play at the US Open, which he took advantage of - solid prize money in New York is relied even for a departure in the first round…</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new1_baseball">Briley St. Clair, a 21-year-old graduate of Mississippi State University, has made a name for herself on social media since the NIL League came into existence.\n He helped the Reds to reach the EuroLeague Final Four and secure the second spot, also winning the Greek championship and cup competition.</string>
    <string name="paragraph3_new2_baseball">— met my request to talk about the Fokine news. \n — We developed this module and handed it over to the Ministry of Education for a long time. Where does this initiative come from, who is climbing across the locomotive there? We have not been able to approve this module for four years. And now someone is trying to plagiarize?\n \n — According to the press service of the Ministry of Education, this is an initiative of physical education teachers.\n \n— Teachers? Who authorized them, who was given the floor there at all? We have signed a cooperation agreement with the Ministry of Education. And we developed this module, a 100-page document is under consideration. It came to a scandal. There is such a Marina Anisimova in the Federal Center of Physical Education. We were kicked off once with this module, the second, the third. There is no way to do this. And now someone is suggesting on the forum.\n \n — I thought I was going to call now — and there you are celebrating: \"Hooray, we made it through!\" \n \n "\"Who are we?\" Physical education teachers? We have an accredited federation. There is no joy, because nothing has been approved. If they said something about something on the forum, it still doesn't mean anything. We didn't make a row, but we were instructed to develop this module. Alexander Yuryevich Kostarev, professor of the Bashkir State Pedagogical University, was engaged in this. And the last time a man simply lost his patience, he talked to Anisimova in raised tones. Well, they answered us something like: \"Oh, you talk like that!\" You know how, if you tell the truth, you will lose your friendship. Here\'s my comment for you.</string>
    <string name="desc_new1_baseball">St. Clair played in all 53 games for Mississippi State, appearing 52 times in the starting lineup. The central defender scored 239 points, becoming the leader of the team.</string>
    <string name="name_basketball1">Luka Doncic</string>
    <string name="name_basketball2">Nikola Vucevic</string>
    <string name="name_basketball3">Shay Gilges-Alexander</string>
    <string name="name_basketball4">Dwarf Jones</string>
    <string name="name_basketball5">Dennis Schroeder</string>
    <string name="name_basketball6">Josh Hawkinson</string>
    <string name="name_basketball7">Andreas Felix</string>
    <string name="name_football1">Eduard Mendigereev</string>
    <string name="name_football2">Karim Benzema</string>
    <string name="name_football3">Robert Lewandowski</string>
    <string name="name_football4">Rafael Leao</string>
    <string name="name_tennis1">Novak Djokovic</string>
    <string name="name_tennis2">Carlos Alcaraz</string>
    <string name="name_tennis3">Daniil Medvedev</string>
    <string name="name_tennis4">Casper Ruud</string>
    <string name="name_tennis5">Taylor Fritz</string>
    <string name="name_baseball1">Shohei Ohtani</string>
    <string name="name_baseball2">Aaron Judge</string>
    <string name="name_baseball3">Mike Trout</string>
    <string name="name_baseball4">Mookie Betts</string>
    <string name="name_baseball5">Trea Turner</string>
    <string name="name_baseball6">Manny Machado</string>
</resources>